theugandanjobline.com 2017-06-13

# PRIVACY POLICY ~ Ugandan Jobline Jobs - The Best Uganda Jobs

### [50 No Experience Sales & Marketing Officer Job Opportunities - Human Resource Service Centre (HRSC) ](http://www.theugandanjobline.com/2017/06/50-fresher-sales-marketing-officer-job-opportunities-human-resource-service-centre-hrsc.html)

Job Title:      Sales & Marketing Officer (50 Fresher Jobs) Organisation: Human Resource Service Centre (HRSC) Duty Station: Kamp... 

This privacy policy sets out how  **Ugandan Jobline Jobs** uses and protects any information that you give  **Ugandan Jobline Jobs** when you use this website.  **Ugandan Jobline Jobs** is very ** _COMMITTED_** to ensuring that your privacy is protected. In case we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, please rest assured that we will only use it only accordance with this privacy statement.  **Ugandan Jobline Jobs** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 8th of April, 2013.

**_What we collect:_**

We may collect the following information:

·         Contact information especially email addresses

**_What we do with the Collected  information:_**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service in meeting the job requirements that match your criteria and also more significantly for the following reasons:

·         Internal Record Keeping

·         We may use the information to improve our products and services.

·         We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

·         From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**_Security:_**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable electronic procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**_Controlling Your Personal information_**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

·         Please send us an E-mail @ [ugandanjobline@gmail.com](mailto:ugandanjobline@gmail.com) to opt out of the E-mail marketing and promotional messages we seldomly send.

·         Please feel free to advise us on Why you are opting out because we value all our visitors even those that are disgruntled with our service.

**_NB_** : We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
